[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
good morning good afternoon and good
evening welcome everyone to Across the
region and across the world we are live
here on LinkedIn and WeChat so if you're
having a good day and you are with us
please hit the like button let us hear
you and let us know that you're having a
great day to our friends in China on
WeChat Nihao to our friends in Japan
konichiwa for everyone else across the
region a very warm welcome a hello and
thank you for joining us for our second
live streaming event here along our
series around lifelong learning
um I encourage all of you to please pop
questions in the chat section and
comments here on LinkedIn and WeChat
throughout our session today and our
topic today as you can see is all around
multi-generational Workforce so if
you're brave and no pressure here why
don't you put in what generation you
might be are you gen Z are you
Millennial what are you
um so why are we here on the LinkedIn
live streaming session well we want to
bring together experts from across the
HR and l d community
and experience with experiences in
multiple Industries to dialogue to
debate and discuss topics close to the
hearts of people development we're going
to have a q a at the end so please put
your questions in the chat and we'll be
ready to respond to them live if not
today we'll definitely be following up
with you and do stay on because we will
have a special lucky dip draw at the end
with some prizes to give away
so to kick things off
we have nihal nangia research director
for the Josh Burson company here to
share the latest trends and insights on
leadership development for a
multi-generational Workforce welcome
nihal
[Music]
hello everyone my name is and I lead
learning and Leadership research at the
Josh person company before we dive deep
into the topic of leadership let's first
take a look at the macroeconomic context
that why leadership and the topic of
leadership development is so important
today
what started as the great resignation in
2020 continues to be a phenomenon that
still rages in full swing the quit rate
which is the percentage of people who
voluntarily quit their jobs every month
is at an all-time high almost three
percent of the workforce is quitting
each month twelve threes are 36 that's
more than a third of the workforce
leaving their jobs this year and of them
two-thirds do not have another job lined
up they're exhausted they don't want to
commit their time and lives to work or
businesses where they don't feel they
have trust and control over what might
suddenly hit them one fine day
we wanted to understand what keeps
people from quitting what is it that has
the highest impact on driving engagement
and retention in creating an employee
experience that will make people stay
so we did an enormous study on employee
experience we studied close to a hundred
practices that impact employee
experience and here's what we saw these
are the top 15 most impactful practices
and if you look closely you'll see those
yellow icons dominating which are all
practices related to trust in the
organization 10 out of the 15 most
impactful employee experience practices
have to do with trust in the
organization transparency empathy
integrity and an inclusive positive work
environment bottom line is people today
need to trust the organization and this
context is extremely important for our
webinar today because in every
organization it is leaders after all
that are the vehicle for building trust
in the organization especially in a
volatile business environment today
making the topic of leadership more
important than ever before
okay I really love this code I recently
came across it and it really resonated
it says in the industry leader jobs were
about the muscles how strong you are
then with the internet and
digitalization came the era of how smart
you are being a knower being right but
in the future jobs will be all about the
heart how much you care and that is
absolutely true for leadership today and
in the future and building on this idea
of trust and care and empathy is this
notion of human-centered leadership
you know you might wonder that there is
no such thing as leading without
thinking about humans but every single
leadership situation decision meeting
and every behavior that a leader
exhibits at work can be thought of as
two parts there's the business part what
is the decision or action that we need
to take to improve the performance of
the company or team or product or
whatever that is
and then there's the Human Side what can
we do or should we do to make the team
more effective to make the individual
more effective to help them learn to
give them an environment where they can
innovate and grow
and what we learned especially from the
pandemic is that during good times you
can focus on the land
but during uncertain times and stressful
times of change you have to focus on the
right organizations need to build
leaders who care you need to build
leaders across Generations regions
career levels across every function team
or segment in your organization
and you need to support leaders on how
to be more empathetic more sensitive and
more inclusive than ever before you need
to teach your leaders to care because
believe it or not the number one reason
why people leave as you can see on my
screen is having leaders who don't care
now let's take a closer look at the
people or the workforce the workforce
today is multi-generational and more
diverse than ever before whether it is a
baby boomer who may be an idealist or a
Gen X who values individualism or a
millennial who might deeply question
things or a gen Z who loves constant
communication the leadership
capabilities that matter the most for
each group whether you are a leader or
what you desire to see in your leader we
found in our research that they all
indeed value the same leadership
capabilities so what are these latest
capabilities that matter
in the old days if you looked at
leadership models they would typically
talk about things like customer
centricity Innovation execution
accountability teamwork
they're all very important but they
don't necessarily create behaviors that
drive trust care and belonging they tell
you what you need to do but they're less
about how you need to act and behave
the leadership capabilities that matter
the most today are what we call power
skills and I'll give you some context on
where these came from there's this group
at UC Berkeley call the greater good
science center in this particular group
studies happiness and they've defined
characteristics or words that create
happiness which are some of the words
that you can see on my screen these are
what we call the power skills of growth
these are not soft skills they're power
skills and these are the skills that
every leader needs and we need to
reinforce these skills in every way
possible recognize and reward these
skills and make them a core element of
our culture because these are the
behaviors you want to Foster in your
leaders and potentially in everyone who
could be a leader all right so how do we
build these new skills how do we build
them in at scale for everyone in the
organization how do we build this new
breed of multi-generational leaders and
also how do we personalized leadership
development
what we recommend and endorse as a
holistic approach to leadership
development is what we refer to as the
six E's
the first e is Envision you need to
start with a Clear Vision what does good
leadership look like in your
organization leadership models are
unique to every organization and they
must mirror the culture mission in
values that you stand for
then the education piece comes in where
you need to put in place formal
trainings and programs to ensure all
leaders know how to get things done and
also how to lead people so for getting
things done you need to train them on
products programs processes policies and
to lead people they need coaching on
Performance Management goal setting how
to give meaningful feedback and how to
mitigate biases but just education isn't
enough because studies tell us that in
barely over a period of 24 hours people
forget 70 of what they learn so you need
to cement learnings from the formalized
trainings and education through
experiences that will help them apply
those learnings in the flow of work so
you need to think about Job rotations
developmental assignments stretch
assignments and international jobs while
some people are born leaders but most
people learn it over time through
experiences and by doing it in
organizations need to facilitate that
the next piece is exposure
some of the best lessons in leadership
come from observing talking with and
getting feedback from others
organizations need to create access to
coaches and mentors and exposure to
outside companies and Senior Executives
vendors like coach Hub can in fact allow
you to have access to a huge network of
coaches in an affordable and scalable
way making this kind of tailored
exposure an opportunity for everyone in
the organization not just a ratified
experience reserved for top of the ram
executives
and then another important piece is
evaluation this is tricky because
particularly if you aren't a good leader
people will rarely ever have the courage
to tell you that you're not a good
leader so we need feedback tools to keep
us honest often we need some forms of
psychological or other forms of
Assessments to see where we have blind
spots coaches can help leaders
self-reflect and understand where they
have rough edges and they can help them
be better leaders
now the final piece once you've created
a Common Language and understanding
around what good leadership means for
your organization and you've given your
leaders the development they need to
build those skills what next
you also need to empower your Leaders
with tools insights and resources that
they need to be effective now if we need
leaders who will empathize and care for
our Workforce we need to start with
caring for our leaders and ensuring that
we are creating capacity for them rather
than adding to their existing workloads
so we need to empower and equip our
leaders with tools that will provide
them with insights in an easy and
consumable way so think about team
Health dashboards action platforms and
productivity tools so essentially you
need to start with defining leadership
what does it mean for your organization
then you need to develop critical
leadership skills you need to Foster the
right behaviors and then you also need
to empower and equip your Leaders with
tools and resources to lead effectively
ultimately what we're saying is
traditional leadership development which
follow this step wise architected
process does not work anymore you need
to build leaders at every level
leadership development today is a
critical enabler of business outcomes
and organizations need to build
leadership capabilities for everyone in
the organization
all right the last thing I want to
quickly talk about before I wrap it up
is the role of Technology
the leadership development Tech Market
is exploding with Solutions all the way
from personalized one-on-one coaching to
life cohort based or group coaching AI
based coaching and nudge technology for
Behavioral Behavior change the metaverse
AR we are in simulation-based platforms
they're redefining leadership
development and they're in fact very
powerful in helping leaders develop
difficult interpersonal skills then
there are platforms that are not really
leadership development tools but they're
a new breed of Performance Management
tools they allow agile goal settings
they show real-time performance data
about individuals and teams they inform
leaders they help them understand where
leaders need to focus and we call them
action platforms of course we're flooded
with content providers that deliver many
types of self-help or self-directed
learning resources on leadership and
then there are platforms that allow
pairings with huge networks of coaches
like coach Hub the coaching Market is
particular slowly flourishing right now
and the fact is when we asked 8 000 HR
Professionals in our Global capability
assessment on what developmental
opportunities they value the most
coaching surface as the most valued
development opportunity
with that I'll hand it over to our panel
to dig deeper on how they're
operationalizing these new models of
leadership building these new
capabilities and developing leaders in
today's diverse multi-generational
Workforce thank you everyone
thank you very much Nihao
[Music]
thank you nihal it's a pleasure to have
heard your insights today so welcome
everyone and let me now introduce our
esteemed panel
um to to answer some questions and have
some discussions on the topics we've had
so welcoming to the to the to the panel
please Linda Liu practice leader of HR
capab culture and sustainability Asia
campus at L'Oreal Lee Murphy group Chief
Human Resources officer FWD insurance we
have Gary hegerty general manager
organizational development from grain
core and Sean tan partner At Mercer
welcome everyone and thank you look
forward to your insights today
so we have three themes that we'll cut
we'll touch on today the first around
breaking down stereotypes so for the
first time ever as we just heard from
nihal there are now four generations
working together in the same workplace
Baby Boomers Generation X Millennials
Generation Z
so the question do workers from
different Generations have wildly
different needs or are they more similar
than we think what's your view let's
start with you Lee
hey thanks Tim and and welcome to
everyone
um you know on this on this session I I
think um the word I wouldn't say wildly
different I think from my own
perspective I've actually been
reflecting on this and uh more similar
than we think I think at the same time
we need to ensure that there are
offerings and a set of experiences that
we provide depending on your life and
career stage
and when I when I think about age as a
number
um we've got to make sure that with
those offerings that in the moments that
matter most to people that that we're
really relevant across the generations
themselves
thanks Lee
um and uh Gary what about you what's
your perspective
um thanks Tim again hello everybody
um very similar to uh to Lee if I'm
honest I think there's a lot of
similarity in what people people want
they want to add value they want to be
kind of contributing to a purpose how
that shows up however could be could be
a little bit differently so the as Lee
mentions the the necessity to
personalize to think of the person to to
construct a solution that matches the
individual as opposed to uh as opposed
to a group
um I think is is absolutely critical
the we will we will often hear the
change of every generation the
entitlement word being thrown around
um personally I think what that boils
down to is more and more knowledge is is
gathered in in early life in in the more
modern
um generations and so therefore there's
there's less passive
um reflection of people are much more
active in in seeking out additional
knowledge contribution purpose and it's
our responsibility really to provide
that
thanks I like what you've said there
around your responsibility in terms of
driving that that passion and purpose
and um and Linda turning to you a
famously uh and and highly sought after
training ground in the Cosmetic space at
L'Oreal how does the uh differing uh
generational Gap play out for you
thanks team hi everyone so very
very own experience so I would like to
share with you my daily work in L'Oreal
Asia campers so usually when learning
and the development project there are
three team members working together so I
as practice leader and I have a project
manager and a coordinator
and may I ask you whether you know
Chinese Zodiac year
so each Chinese so that year is
represented by an animal each Chinese
zodiac sign is decided by our first year
so I would like to share with you there
are three tigers in my project team
but we are not at the same age
the possibility you can guess our age
now
so I'm the oldest my PM in the middle
and the learning coordinate and text
support she is the youngest
so actually we are totally different
even we are Chinese we were born in
different times growing different toward
economic situations and studying
different school and majors and also we
have different strengths and characters
different life purpose and motive to the
task
but actually I discovered that we have
some common needs our way to make
effective and happy teamwork
for example we all want to be connected
and feel the belongings belong to the
same project team
and also we would like to clarify each
each people each each everyone in the
team our key responsibilities and how to
leverage our strengths
and we would like to speak up openly and
challenge each other
for the status quo but with good purpose
and also we would like to not only
working for the project I mean working
for L'Oreal the organization but I also
want to learn and grow by practice so
every time we want we we always ask
ourselves what the project means to me
hope that it can also support our own
growth
so that's my sharing
thank you some really excellent
perspectives there and um one as I think
about the topic around
multi-generational Workforce um a theme
that's coming to mind is obviously the
Aging Workforce
um uh there's research from PWC it's
estimated that us 3.5 trillion dollars
could be added to oecd Country economies
just by encouraging this Golden Age
workers or older workers to stay a few
years longer in the workforce or perhaps
return and bring their skills back to
back to the organization Sean turning to
you what are the common misconceptions
around this Golden Age segment in your
in your mind
thank you Tim hi everybody I'm Sean it's
very nice to be here
um so indeed there may be some
misconceptions about people in the
golden age in that some may suffer from
you know deterioration and physical and
cognitive abilities and these things may
limit their ability to contribute also
that some are obstinate uh some may not
even some may even be derogative to
others because they think they know more
than others
um there is a Chinese phrase that I hear
from time to time coming from such
individuals when literally translated it
means that I have eaten more salt than
you have eaten rice the image of this is
rather ludicrous if you ask me but this
is essentially a dismissive way of
implying that there are a lot more
experienced than others and hence know a
lot more these things are not helpful so
if I ever feel tempted to say something
like this I need to remind myself to
think again
um the other Generations also have
received their share of misconceptions
some refer to the Millennials and
Genesis as the strawberry generation
which implies that they are soft and not
resilient also that they are entitled
and we covered a little bit of that just
now because things came to them easy
when they were growing up they belong to
the era of you know participation
trophies but allow me to come back to my
first point on a change in cognitive
abilities with age there is an
increasing body of research that breaks
down cognitive abilities into two
subcategories
the first is what we call Fluid
cognitive ability this reflects an
individual's capacity to process
information and solve Level problems
now this type of cognitive ability does
show some decline beyond the 40s the
second is known as crystallized
cognitive ability this involves the
ability to deduce secondary relational
ideas by applying previously learned
relational ideas and visibility in
effect keeps going up over time and does
not come down until very very much later
in life I I shun you know specify how
much data in life so in essence I think
it is important to take a more
circumspect view when considering this
topic
thanks Sean thank you
um and Lee perhaps uh turning back to
you as you think about the career that
you've LED and the organizations that
you've had the ability to be a leader at
um what are some of the anecdotes or
experiences that you can share with us
in terms of approaches to these
differing Talent segments in your own
experience
yeah look I think I think when thinking
about the Golden Age
um and and certainly those closer to
retiring age
we're certainly looking at that closely
because we're actually people are living
longer the medical technology the
quality of life and also people want
more you know in even longer in their
careers to extend those careers as well
and I think from an organizational view
we need to make sure that those
offerings and opportunities being an
inclusive workplace are actually there
so I think one one
um you know practical part is when we're
looking at Japan
where often the retirement age has been
60 you lose a lot of good talent at that
time a lot of expertise technical or
otherwise it's been built up laid upon
as such and I think from our perspective
you know we're extending uh the
retirement age to 65.
but also looking at 70 uh in the in the
Japanese context and that that's
significant uh when you start to think
about the longevity that you're putting
for people's careers but also the signal
that's sending to some of the younger
Generations on how they start to think
about the pacing of their career and the
life stages if you give certainty in the
way that you look at lengthening your
careers people can plan around that in
terms of in and out opting in and out
the way that look at their Career
Development the way they Pace their
professional development as well so I'm
actually very excited about how we
extend for those who want it you know
within the workplace as well I think
it's really important and part of that
is providing flexible
working practices and it's something
that we look at
um in in terms of the way we package the
hours as well for people so I think
there's actually a huge opportunity from
a HR perspective when we look at our
benefits mix but also our Flex working
optionality as well so for me the sort
of thought leadership and research is
going to be really required over the
next couple of years in terms of how we
look at this for our Workforce
thanks team thanks thank you Lee
um pace of change I I really I wrote
that one down I think that's a really
interesting uh comment that you've said
and how we Flex we must we must Flex for
these different Talent segments so if
you've got a point of view here or a
question related to how you've managed
the pace of change make sure you put
that in our comments so we can address
that later today
so let's Orient the conversation now to
Talent segments the segments at risk we
spoke about generational
um segments of what about thinking about
the talent population as a whole
um perhaps thinking you know that
Blended zodiac approach that Linda
shared with us a moment ago
um perhaps starting with you Linda um
with all that we've heard from nihal and
considering your talent population as a
whole what segment is most at risk for
you in your organization right now and
and why
so from my personal perspectives in the
organizations that the business and
function leaders especially at the
middle level they have a big pressure
now
because for example our new vision of
leadership for L'Oreal is the role of a
manager is both to lead and to enable
others to strive
so I feel a lot of time pressures for
those this group of people the managers
the leaders the people leaders
also in L'Oreal you put you play the
role as entrepreneur it's not enough
you just run the bin as well that's fine
that's necessary but not enough
so leaders also and should be an
innovator
so invent the do the Innovation and the
creative ideas for the life changing in
the beauty for the consumers Beauty
experience
that's why L'Oreal can keep the top one
position in the building industry
worldwide and also leaders should have
strategic thinking to shape the future
and make the way for people to follow
you and so you needed how to say
to create the sense of purpose
with Clear Vision and Mission
and also now we don't um how to say
promote individual Heroes so in L'Oreal
team is hero
so how to integrate how to cut clap do
the collaboration across team
for the whole organization's agility
that's the essential for L'Oreal now
so not only know the diversity Equity
inclusion by the methodology but how to
behave how to become the role modeling
as an inclusive leader
and also the the this group of managers
also needed to spend time with their
teams even you have a big team or small
team you need to spend time with them
have regular dialogue with them to grow
them to understand their purpose and to
understand how to motivate them because
L'Oreal believe grow the people first
then we can grow our business
so you see the these group people need
to do many things
so and also for themselves they needed
to do the leadership up Skilling and the
reschooling also taking care of their
well-being
so I really hope that shr we can support
the physical people as much as possible
sharing the mid manager segment
um turning to you Gary
across the business that you manage tell
us a little bit about the segments that
are on top of Mind as a risk for you
right now
um I I've got a certainly got a lot of
similarity to what uh what what Linda
shared
um regarding the the kind of evolution
of a for the leader and the expectations
of a leader
um with regards to the talent segments
that we feel at risk I think the reality
is all of them
um there is there is a high demand on on
Talent here in Australia we've got
nearly as many jobs advertisers we have
in unemployed in the entire country
record record lows we've got
um therefore more desperate employers
coming to coming to the table so you've
got kind of the choice and people can
choose or to go or stay they can choose
to to join or leave so the the
challenges I guess is is the risk is are
you relevant are you a business that
people want to be a part of that they
can relate to uh and they can feel that
they contributes both
um personally and professionally
um and that kind of whole version of
work-life integration
so so with that that in mind and we've
we've certainly touched on that and and
Linda talking about the the individual
requirement the individual connection
that we uh the leaders that need with
with their team I think we've got to
create a individual and personalized
reason to either to join or stay so our
our bigger challenge comes to the
shifting mentality the shifting
um shifting behavioral skill set that
that is is a leader versus a manager so
what are we doing day in day out that
makes people want to follow makes people
want to be part of the story makes
people want to be to be proud to to to
build a legacy so it's No One Singular
Talent segment and I think that's that's
actually the right thing because every
Talent segment is at risk but every
Talent segment is a great opportunity if
we can get everything lined up
um there is an incredibly changing view
of tenure
so greencorp is a large agribusiness
it's a well-known and well-established
Australian brand with a global presence
and with most agricultural backgrounds
farming backgrounds tenure is a big
thing 10 20 30 40 years plus
with the the significant moves
particularly
um Gen Y so Millennials and geriatric
Millennials and gen Z in terms of the
tenure being cut down to about three
years and so that shifting view of what
are we getting from the three years and
how do you create more careers within
one business again has the opportunity
to to drive lifelong learning leadership
capability leadership connection
um but real purpose for individuals to
be part of it
thanks Gary
um really uh great insights and
observation for what's going on at your
company and Lee uh when we connected
ahead of this conversation you shared
with us you're also facing this Talent
crisis being more acute than before do
you mind sharing us a little bit about
what that impact is for your business
yeah look if I can just just build off
Gary and and Linda's commentary which I
I support fully I think um in my working
career I have not seen the Dynamics in
the talent side
um it's actually extraordinary what
we're going through and I think the key
words not necessarily challenge but
opportunity and how you turn this
um from a mindset perspective I think
all Talent segments are at risk
depending on the cycle you're in you
know with critical roles some can be a
more risk at others but at the same time
early in career you know we run
particular digital programs graduate
programs you know
constantly at risk
um and you know having to re-recruit you
know some of our more experienced
managers as well it's it's a constant in
terms of each each of the segments
um as well I think BCG
um and and many may have heard this but
I think it's you know maybe
um misquoting but at least you know
um
the talent crisis is over talent has won
so the actual power dynamics have
shifted
you know to to the employee more so than
from the organization and I think from
that perspective
you can't it's not BAU so and it's
actually
um in some cases acute but at the other
stage it's also dripping away and what I
mean by that is it's slowly eroding in
certain areas and and strategically
you have to have a different series of
interventions you know in terms of your
talent governance
making sure that you're well integrated
with your lnd
programs as such we heard the the words
alignment with your purpose and vision
uh from that perspective as well so I
think
also when you look at your initiatives
that we're spending a lot of time from
an FWD perspective we're pan-Asian
um insurer
all in Asia 10 markets so how do we
actually get you know the internal
Talent Marketplace operating effectively
making sure that we provide those career
and professional development
opportunities so that's a big one so
which do you have a build or a buy
strategy is it Blended so we're going
through all those iterations and at the
same time
we're looking for more sophisticated you
know Talent sourcing models so how do we
how do we scan the markets how do we get
sets of diverse experiences that may not
be in the insurance industry and
bringing them in and then the onboarding
and the stickiness that's required as
well because Gary hit on something
around Kenya
and that that tenure piece where you had
that predictable two to three years or
four years enroll those those those
times are going
things are more Dynamic
um as well but also other employers may
only be looking at that you have three
to six months experience and they're
willing to bring you on into their
company so the tenure piece is actually
irrelevant more and more as as I look
across across the industry so I'll just
pause on that Tim but that's that's
that's a few thoughts
thanks Lee
um really good observations from
everyone so segments of the population
we're seeing are all generally at risk
I'll anchor on uh the comments that
Linda shared
um on a pressing need around mid
managers we certainly hear that in the
conversations we're having across the
region is this pressure uh for many of
our mid managers to respond to to the
need so pressure from the top in terms
of business but also managing the
day-to-day expectations of that
Workforce of those that talent that
expects to be promoted within three
months or the family you know the person
who has to identify and manage their
work life from home in this hybrid
hybrid Workforce so certainly hearing
this sense of of pressure our mid
managers Microsoft just released a
report
um recently their work Trend index that
said 76 of employ of mid manager
employees said that they would stay at
their company longer if they could
benefit from more Learning and
Development support and combined with
that we also see before I Turn to You
Sean thinking about CEO interest the
research that we've seen recently from
from research the Global Leadership
forecast says 55 of CEOs say leadership
development is their number one priority
and so Sean you know you've been a group
chro previously you've held senior
leadership roles at GIC at gov Tech now
you're at Mercer Consulting with CEOs
and clients across the region what are
you what are you hearing from CEOs
around leadership development and why
this is a priority for them
yeah so Tim as we look at our latest
Google talent Trends uh study for the
year of 2022 we see that more than four
out of five CEOs are saying that the
business agenda and the people agenda
have never been more intertwined
um business success more than ever is
going to be now dependent on how the
people agenda is being Advanced and
leadership development is a key part in
the people agenda
relatedly rescaling and upskilling is
also one of the workforce initiatives
that both the HR leadership group and
the executives group believe would
generate the highest business impact
furthermore leadership development
boosts Employee Engagement increases the
organization's ability to deal with
Talent gaps in the talent Pipeline and
reduces the pain and costs associated
with turnover so we are really seeing a
time and turnover is is really really
high and the cost of doing business is
increasing people are having also a lot
more choices if you look at the latest
data coming from the Singapore Ministry
of Manpower we are looking at the ratio
of 3.53 vacancies for every one job
Seeker so this is really a time of
choices for for talent and I do agree
that uh
um the the tenant crisis is over and
talent the talent population has won so
organizations really need effective
leaders to retain and inspire people to
go their extra mile to become the
greatest versions of themselves so as to
drive the best commercial outcomes for
organizations and under such a trying
conditions
Talent crisis is over and the talent
population is one I think that's out
that has to be our tagline for today's
discussion
um Lee what about you are you hearing
the same from your CEO our Business
Leaders
um is it is it a challenge and being
um exhibited and communicated in that in
that same strength in your in your
organization
yeah I think um moving from challenge to
opportunity so clearly our CEO sponsors
in fact a a senior leadership
development program that we hold twice a
year Forum 55 and we make you know
significant investments from a
leadership development perspective and
we also have a university programs
foundational programs but Belinda's
earlier point you know our focus at
scale has been on our people managers
and you know to lead through through
these times as you said the pressure
never been more short-term focused
long-term strategic so one of our
pillars of our people and organizational
strategy as leaders reimagined
and you can go on for a lot in in that
space But in the people manager space we
look at different interventions we run
Master Class series
where we have
um our executive team you know opening
those series we've had
you know 1 800 manager participants over
the last 12 months which is
extraordinary and that focuses on
engagement and Effectiveness but when we
look at the core of our manager and
leader development programs it's lead
yourself lead your team lead your
business and and keep the Simplicity and
Clarity of that and make sure that
you're you know supporting in relation
to all those needs because if you can't
lead yourself then you can't lead your
team or your business and I see this
self-care you'll see that language
coming in more self-care
uh the well-being uh side of of the work
in terms of how you just support the
emotional physical social connectedness
um of our leaders as well and I'm
actually very excited about how the team
has been developing that space and we've
got both the CEO's support investment
and time in the way that uh that we're
pursuing these these areas
thank you Lee
um reflecting on nihal's commentary uh
in the presentation that started she
mentioned um investments in people
development and so on are shifting gears
as so much as forgotten after people
leave a classroom and hence coaching
being the top priority in in her
commentary for people development
initiatives and
um the the piece you mentioned around
well-being women in leadership as well
as inclusive leadership these being the
top three trends that we've seen from a
coach Hub uh Global buyers survey
looking at people who buy coaching
services and the problems they're
looking to solve what's what's
encouraging is that nine out of ten HR
leaders have committed to investing
further in coaching as a way to improve
these Talent segments and populations as
a whole so shifting to shifting gears a
little bit and thinking about how do you
develop leadership skills across a
hybrid multi-generational Workforce and
create a continuous lifelong learning
culture Gary if I can call on you you've
worked with you're working with Coach
Hub right now on a leadership
development program perhaps you could
share more about that program itself and
um and and what you're looking to solve
through that partnership
um come to me with the easy questions
Tim hey
um so uh look there's many ways there's
many ways to look at this I think
historically when we look at leadership
development it's very much attendance
equals competence
um and so you'd disappear for a couple
of days into a classroom and suddenly
the the ales of the world were cured
um as as um as as Linda mentioned as
nihil mentioned in terms of the
retention of that that knowledge it's
it's it's minimal at best I think so the
the shift in the shifting way that
people absorb knowledge is very
different being able to connect with
people is is is very different what
we've we've tried to look at is that
multi multifaceted Blended approach to
to leadership capability with that shift
in mindset of what actually is
leadership
um I just made I made a couple of notes
that we talk about
um effective leadership and that
Effectiveness has
I'll I'll show the tracks here a little
bit the our view of effective leadership
has changed over the last five years so
an effective leader was one who
delivered results
I don't think we've got any any doubt in
that however an effective leader now is
is governed by the impact that they have
on those who follow them those who who
are around them the Legacy that they're
building that has a positive impact not
only on on the business that they're
employed with but their overall life so
on average the average adult spends I
believe it's 90 000 hours in work that's
quite a significant amount so as Leaders
what can we do to create a positive
environment where that 90 000 hours are
adding benefit to you to your family to
your life to to everything around you so
when we we looked at the The Wider
partnership uh coach had been being part
of that it was it was looking at
different segments of leadership to
create a Common Language so whether
that's about leadership impact whether
that's about consideration
um whether it's care so going back to
the areas in in nihal's um presentation
about about care and also looking at the
reason people leave is because they
don't have a caring manager
so we we looked at what can we do to
create connection and a leadership
capability that is genuinely
you are here for your people
now those who have maybe heard me talk
before I've simplified this even further
and I'll try not to to be a crude
leadership comes down to
don't be just don't be don't be bad to
people be nice that's the most
simplistic way we can look at it so
that's how we we focus a lot of our
impact-based leadership of considering
what have you done today to build a
legacy that's positive for you and those
around you
coach Hub also offers us the opportunity
to to take the face-to-face elements and
scale them up with ongoing uh goal
setting goal attainment it's a scalable
solution it's taken us away from just
this attendance equals competence it
brings an embedding aspect to things but
when I look at coaching on a more
holistic level for far too long it's
just been the domain of the the the
privilege view it's been a premium tool
offered to a few people at the top table
maybe those on the talent programs and
then it stops we are really Keen to
democratize that's what as wide as as we
possibly can everybody should should
benefit from from professional and
experience and exceptional coaching that
has to be in tandem with so many other
things but it's a key step forward from
from where we've we've been in the past
tense so in in a nutshell it's about
managing that Blended approach so you
have the the education element that Lee
Hill told about you have the exposure
been able to put things into practice
but the reflection the refinement the
feedback the and then the the pivot and
go again the coaching and feedback and
regular dialogue dialogue brings that
for us I believe is is going to support
the changing face of leadership and
support the expectations that we all
have
thanks Gary it's an exciting journey and
thank you for sharing it and thanks for
sharing it with us Linda I'd love to
turn over to you flag May how are you
driving leadership development and a
lifelong learning culture at L'Oreal
um
thanks teams I totally agree with what
Lee and Gary shared I think leadership
is always the the most popular topics in
the in our Learning and Development
world so in L'Oreal we have to leave we
have the leadership and culture
University so we provide uh the program
many many programs to support the
managers in their transition moment for
example transition to people manager
transition to team manager transition to
function head of function transition to
GM transition to Executive leaders
transition to Zone leaders this is the
new program we will launch after the
national holiday
so you see a lot of programs to support
the leaders to grow and to face uh
different expectations from the
organizations and to face the different
scenarios in their career growth
and besides this we also give the
freedom to our leaders and employees to
have the flex programs every year they
can free them they can have they free
they have the freedom to pick up one
program in the catalog
to for their personal growth
and uh it's this is from the um the the
knowledge and the skill size and I
totally agree with Gary that leaders
they also need the most difficult part
is self-awareness how to help leaders to
impose their self-awareness
to really uh go outside of their limited
beliefs
so coach is really powerful tools so in
L'Oreal we provide the coaching
essential programs for not only the hrp
piece but all the people leaders
and we also provide coaching tools for
hrd and also for the senior leaders to
help them to further develop their
coaching skills and we also have the
program called codef codef actually in
the market is is a kind of peer coaching
Collective coaching so let the leaders
to share their pain points and
challenges with each other in a safe
environment and help each other
we called share and the care
lots of lots of head nods today I'm I'm
loving that everyone seems to be in
agreement on the panel on well-being and
on purpose and on making life easy from
a learning opportunity right
um Lee did you have something to add
yeah I think um just more on the
lifelong learning culture piece I think
I went through the leadership
development piece earlier and you know I
actually really enjoyed hearing Linda
and Gary a moment ago and I thought
democratizing coaching to the many
rather than the few
um you know really resonated strongly
from that perspective I think on the
lifelong learning culture and I'm
working with our head of l d at the
moment and our head of talent how to
embed that in your organization is is is
is is The Sweet Spot that we that we're
going for
um and you know I was thinking about
time and space how do you create that
space within your organization for those
moments and then how do you role model
the time
you know in in creating time for your
leaders to have because that's the most
valuable commodity at the moment is is
time and you know there's a series of
trade-offs as you look at your lifelong
learning culture and I think just two
proof points there one is
um self-paced learning so we've we've
got we're using technology that we heard
earlier you know from nehal and we're
using a mobile app you know through our
manager Essentials program that that
we've developed in-house and with a with
a partner and gamification with that
socially connecting amongst the leaders
as well but leveraging the technology
for that self-paced and peer-supported
learning is absolutely critical so that
they get to huddle together through that
and that's that's taken a really good
take up from that perspective and the
other piece is is is back to Gary's
point on um we want to create also
amongst our people leaders and people
managers a coaching culture
and that takes years to actually
deploy embed and then practice and role
model and you've got to provide that
environment you know for that to occur
as well and I'm looking forward to how
we take that out and probably the third
one is on the lifelong learning you can
talk about it but you actually need to
put you know demonstrated models in
place so we're looking at an anytime
learning concept
uh you know for all our people
and providing them with opportunities
both on bespoke
uh you know using Ai and other ways to
make sure that the relevant course gets
to you in a timely manner
self-paced in in the way that you learn
but also tied to your your your
development and career plan as well so
it's sort of joining the dots in a
holistic way to bring that to to our
people
fantastic thank you thanks Tim and
sharing from everyone for sharing your
your ideas and your vision and how
you're responding to today's challenge
you know lately um summarized it but our
mission at coach Hub is to democratize
coaching to people of all levels
worldwide and doing that at scale at
ease removing any friction and giving
access to individual employees a coach
in their pocket to the top five percent
business coaches globally and and being
able to see those proven results and be
able to work on a lot of those
purpose-driven areas
um so it's been a pleasure to hear from
so many of you today I think we've got a
real sense of the commitment you each
have of driving to that people
development culture and the visions that
you're building for the the generational
Workforce we live in we really
appreciate it I'd love to turn over to
sub q a because we have had some coming
through uh the the chat box and the
comment section on we uh WeChat and
Linkedin so let me quickly um address
one we have a question uh that came
through from Andre we hear many leaders
are struggling to reskill their
Workforce to keep up with the demands of
disruption what can we do to support
leaders organizations and individuals to
drive skills transitions to prepare for
the future Sean perhaps I I Turn to You
what what are you Consulting on or
speaking about on this front
yeah thanks Tim um I think Gary Linda
and Lee headed super well cupboard so
maybe I'll just talk a little bit about
the organization perspective and maybe
the attitudinal aspects for individuals
um really the way that we look at
lifelong learning is that it's part of a
broader agenda of continued Workforce
transformation and Workforce
transformation is about redesigning jobs
it's about reskilling people retooling
job holders and also very importantly
reframing mindsets and organizations
could review employees who are in
at-risk jobs and look for skills that
overlap with the hard to feel vacancies
and then map a learning Pathway to help
people move from one job family to
another
um another possibility is to introduce
skills-based pay across the employee
life cycle uh in parallel to also
understand the market value and
availability of in-demand skills and
then incentivize efforts to acquire such
skills as well as the application of
such skills in in projects
um one other way is also to evolve the
entire Talent infrastructure to now use
skills as the new currency and this is
where AI becomes a particularly useful
to match skills to tasks and also to
take into account
adjacencies or skills now doing this
would allow employees to know that
skills is now the basis for continued
employment and now you know that will in
a way give them healthy pressure to go
and pursue the skills that are needed to
stay employed
um and the skills they possess now
become open knowledge within the
Enterprise people would then you know be
a lot more motivated to to engage in and
continue and lifelong learning very
importantly at the individual level I
feel as part of this construct a few
conditions need to be in place first
there must be confidence right that this
can be done secondly and and this is
something that I cannot over emphasize
there must be humility to never stop
learning irrespective of who you are who
you think you are and whom you are
learning from or how you're learning
thirdly a general curiosity because the
world's problems are now you know much
more complex and the ability to solve
those problems would not exist within a
single person or a single company or a
single nation for that matter
suffice to see Solutions increasing me
to take a more transdisciplinary nature
and we really need people to come
together and have an equal voice to
contribute irrespective of status age or
anything any sort of labeling that may
separate us
thanks Sean thank you a great response
there but one more and I'm going to put
it to Gary
um it's from uh JJ how do you get the
leader's buy-in that they need the
leadership coaching
um it's a really good question
um I think many leaders believe that
they are already there well however we
look at it and because I got this
position for me so why would I change
it's it's about and it probably links to
what what Sean was saying as well it's
what's the what's the intrinsic drivers
why are people doing the role what do
they want to remember for what what do
they
um what do they remember what do they
forget what would they like other people
to to recall we do a very simple
exercise
um I I refer to we've all worked for
leaders who we would walk over broken
glass to work for again that is a
positive impact
we've all worked for leaders who would
happily stamp into that broken glass
never to see a game they've had that
kind of impact on us as well so we do a
very simple exercise of your fast
forward 18 months two years
congratulations you're an amazing leader
you're leaving you've got a better job a
bigger job more complex role what's the
leaving speech that your team have
written for you what do you want to be
remembered for what is the Legacy you're
creating that then becomes the
aspirational goal and each and every day
we ask them to look at that what did
that what what did you what is your
aspiration what is your legacy I wanted
to create what are you doing today that
delivers a game start
the important part here is
there's no point of saying this is what
you need to be this is what you need to
do the key part with any motivational
driver is these are your words this is
what you have said is important this is
what you want to be remembered for what
are you doing about it
Gary great response any other comments
from the panel
no okay
um fantastic it's been an amazing
experience here thank you so much
hearing about
um the passion that you bring into uh
into your conversations into your
workplaces into the leadership profiles
that you're you're developing and
grooming in your organization so thank
you Linda thank you Sean Gary and Lee
for your time today we really appreciate
it and it's been great learning and
hearing from you all
that is now the moment that you've all
been waiting for for those still on the
line uh it is our surprise pleasure
Lucky Draw we're giving away Amazon and
jd.com gift e-cards and books there's
only five lucky winners um from our
registrations today and you do actually
have the option to not receive the gift
e-cards and books and instead have us
coach Hub plant trees in your local
community on behalf of our CSR partner
ecosia so the drumroll please
okay our winners
we have deep dish such Deva from Westpac
group in Australia rupali parasani from
Samsung Electronics in India Michael
Gann from Acom in Shanghai and he swam
from LF Logistics in Hong Kong and Jai
Dev Ram Mohan from DBS Bank in Singapore
congratulations to all the winners we'll
be reaching out to you individually and
thank you for joining us today thank you
everyone for joining us today please
give us your feedback your thoughts in
the comments section here on LinkedIn or
WeChat and continue to follow us follow
our channels on LinkedIn and WeChat for
updates for our third and final session
on the lifelong learning series which
will take place 27th of October
featuring top coaches in the region and
Senior HR leaders from gov Tech society
generale and
asmpt it's been a pleasure to have you
thank you very much for your attendance
today have a great day ahead
foreign
[Music]
Linda
foreign
[Music]
yes
foreign
[Music]